const structure = [
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 1',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 2',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 3',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 4',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 5',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 6',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 7',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 8',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 9',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 10',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 11',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 12',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 13',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 14',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: 'Вопрос 15',
        a: 'Вариант 1',
        b: 'Вариант 2',
        c: 'Вариант 3',
        d: 'Вариант 4',
        answer: 'd'
    }
];